THE PRAYER WILL BE OFFERED BY
CHAPLAIN GIBBONS.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: WOULD YOU PRAY WITH
ME? GOD, OUR PROVIDER, ALL THAT
WE NEED. YOU SUPPLY THE
STRENGTH THAT WE REQUIRE FOR
THE DAYS AHEAD. YOU MAKE
AVAILABLE TO US. WE NEED ONLY
PREPARE THE TABLE OF OUR LIVES
TO RECEIVE YOU IN OUR MIDST. WE
NEED ONLY OPEN OUR SOULS TO
RECEIVE THE WISDOM OF YOUR WORD.
WE NEED ONLY EMPTY OURSELVES OF
OUR PRIDE TO ACKNOWLEDGE THAT
WHAT WE REALLY NEED IS YOU.
SATISFY THEN OUR HUNGER FOR
TRUTH AND HONESTY, FOR PEACE
AND UNITY, FOR YOUR WISDOM AND
GUIDANCE. THIS DAY AND IN THE
WEEKS TO COME. THE STRENGTH OF
YOUR NAME WE PRAY. AMEN.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: PURSUANT TO CLAUSE
13 OF RULE ONE, THE JOURNAL OF
THE LAST DAY'S PROCEEDINGS IS
APPROVED. THE CHAIR WILL LEAD
THE HOUSE IN THE PLEDGE OF
ALLEGIANCE. I PLEDGE ALLEGIANCE.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: TO THE FLAG OF THE
UNITED STATES OF AMERICA AND TO
THE REPUBLIC FOR WHICH IT
STANDS. ONE NATION UNDER GOD,
INDIVISIBLE, WITH LIBERTY AND
JUSTICE FOR ALL.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: THE CHAIR WILL
RECEIVE A MESSAGE.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: MR. SPEAKER.
MESSAGES FROM THE SENATE.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: MADAM SECRETARY.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: I HAVE BEEN DIRECTED
BY THE SENATE TO INFORM THE
HOUSE THAT THE SENATE HAS
PASSED S5 28, AN ACT TO
REAUTHORIZE THE GREAT LAKES
RESTORATION INITIATIVE AND FOR
THE PURPOSES IN WHICH THE
CONCURRENCE OF THE HOUSE IS
REQUESTED.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: THE CHAIR ANNOUNCES
THE SPEAKER'S APPOINTMENT
PURSUANT TO TWO U.S.C. 1151 A
AND THE ORDER OF THE HOUSE OF
JANUARY 3RD, 2025. THE
FOLLOWING MEMBER ON THE PART OF
THE HOUSE TO THE BOARD OF
TRUSTEES OF THE CONGRESSIONAL
OFFICE FOR INTERNATIONAL
LEADERSHIP.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: MR. CASE OF HAWAII.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: THE CHAIR ANNOUNCES
THE SPEAKER'S APPOINTMENT
PURSUANT TO 20 U.S.C. TEN, 11,
10 OR 11 OR 1011 C AND THE
ORDER OF THE HOUSE OF JANUARY
3RD, 2025 WITH THE FOLLOWING
INDIVIDUALS ON THE PART OF THE
HOUSE TO THE NATIONAL ADVISORY
COMMITTEE ON INSTITUTIONAL
QUALITY AND INTEGRITY FOR A
TERM OF SIX YEARS.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: UPON THE
RECOMMENDATION OF THE MINORITY
LEADER, MR. ROBERT SHEARMAN.
OAKLAND, CALIFORNIA MISS
DOMINIQUE BAKER, WILMINGTON,
DELAWARE.
UNIDENTIFIED SPEAKER: PURSUANT TO CLAUSE
13 OF RULE ONE, THE HOUSE
STANDS ADJOURNED UNTIL 4 P.M.
TOMORROW.